听力材料一：情景反应。根据你所听到的句子，选择恰当的应答语。
1. Bill, thanks a lot for helping me with my English.
thanks a lot for helping me with my English.
2. Lily, let's make a card for dad as a birthday gift.
let's make a card for dad as a birthday gift.
3. Sally, you look so beautiful in the new skirt.
Sally, you look so beautiful in the new skirt.
4. Hey, Cindy, what's the weather like today?
Hey, Cindy, what's the weather like today?
5. Eric, could you please go for a walk with me after lunch?
Eric, could you please go for a walk with me after lunch?
对话问答：根据你所听到的对话及问题，选择正确答案。
6. I usually go to work at 6 o in the morning.
Really? That's so early.
Question. What time does the man usually go to work?
I usually go to work at 6 o in the morning.
Really? That's so early.
Question. What time does the man usually go to work?
Excuse me, could you tell me the way to the bookstore?
Sure, it's on Center Street next to the bank.
Question. Where is the man going?
Excuse me, could you tell me the way to the bookstore?
Sure, it's on Center Street next to the
Question. Where is the man going?
8. do you have art lessons at school?
Yes, I have art lessons on Tuesday.
Question. When does Lucy have art lessons?
Lucy, do you have art lessons at school?
Yes, I have art lessons on Tuesday.
Question. When does Lucy have art
9. don't be late for class next time.
Sorry, Mr. I won't.
Question. Who is talking to Nancy?
Nancy, don't be late for class next time.
Sorry, Mr. Clark, I won't.
Question. Who is talking to Nancy?
10. Hello, this is Tony speaking.
Hi, Tony. Could I speak to Grace please?
Oh, she's not at home.
She is playing volleyball outside.
What is Grace doing now?
Hello, this is Tony speaking.
Hi, Tony. Could I speak to Grace please?
Oh, she's not at home.
She is playing volleyball outside.
Question. What is Grace doing now?
三，图片理解，看图听描述。数，选择与你所听到的描述内容相符合的选项。下列图中有一幅图片与描述内容无关。
Question. Question. Question.
Question. Question.
Jim started to play basketball at the age of
Jim started to play basketball at the age of five.
Question. Question.
Question. Question. Question.
四短文理解。根据你所听到。到的短文内容，判断下列各句正误。
Question. Question.
Question. Question. Question.
Question.